excitedigitalmedia.com 2012-09-19

# Excite Digital Media | Excite Digital Media

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Excite Digital Media collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a 'User') of the Network and all products and services offered by Excite Digital Media. 

## Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users: visit our network, register on the network, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, use services, features or resources we make available on our Network. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, their name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information, and social security number. Users may, however, visit our Network anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

## Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about, the disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Network.

## Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Network or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

## Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Network that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site(s). In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

## Advertising

Ads appearing on our network may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non- personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, amongst other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

## Rubicon

Some of the ads may be served by Rubicon. A Rubicon cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Network and other sites on the Internet. Rubicon uses 'non personally identifiable information' and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the Rubicon cookie by visiting the Rubicon ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.rubiconproject.com/privacy-policy/>

## Zedo

Some of the ads may be served by Zedo. A Zedo cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Network and other sites on the Internet. Zedo uses 'non personally identifiable information' and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the Rubicon cookie by visiting the Zedo ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.zedo.com/about-zedo/privacy-policy/>

## Changes to this privacy policy

Excite Digital Media has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

## Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Network, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Network. Your continued use of the Network following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed by us to be your acceptance of those changes.

## Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this network, or your dealings with this network, please contact us at:  
Excite Digital Media  
www.excitedigitalmedia.com  
Suite 1901, Westfield Tower 2  
101 Grafton St, Bondi Junction  
NSW, Australia 2022  
Phone: +61 2 8061 2950  
Email: display@excitedigitalmedia.com

_This document was last updated on February 14, 2012_
